<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Software on Go In Action</title><link>http://goinaction.github.io/software/</link><description>Recent content in Software on Go In Action</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://goinaction.github.io/software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>IDEs and Editors</title><link>http://goinaction.github.io/software/editors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://goinaction.github.io/software/editors/</guid><description>In order to write source code, you need something to type it into. You can of course use any text editor for this, but we highly recommend an Integrated Development Environment, or at least a pluggable text editor designed with writing code in mind.
IDEs An Integrated Development Environment (&amp;ldquo;IDE&amp;rdquo;) is a program that provides a comprehensive environment for writing code. The line between IDE and Code editor can sometimes get a little blurry, but generally IDEs provide a richer, more dedicated experience with features such as integrated, graphical debugging, test annotations, and integrated terminals.</description></item><item><title>Terminal Emulators</title><link>http://goinaction.github.io/software/terminals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://goinaction.github.io/software/terminals/</guid><description>Terminal emulators, are so-called because they &amp;ldquo;emulate&amp;rdquo; the experience of using a terminal interface, whether or not your sustem has one built in. But, really, they are often much more than that, and some of them provide a lot of sophisticated functionality to make the experience flexible, powerful and convenient.
The following is a (far from exhaustive) list of some popular terminal emulators you might want to consider when doing work on the command line.</description></item><item><title>Git</title><link>http://goinaction.github.io/software/git/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://goinaction.github.io/software/git/</guid><description>Git Homepage
Git is a source control management tool, which allows people to collaborate on software development. It is used internally by the Go tool for downloading dependencies and other tools. Depending on the other software you install from this list, you may find that it is installed for you automatically, but if you need it, this is the place to go.</description></item></channel></rss>